<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ClimateHopeFund</string>
    <string name="menu_open">Drawer Open</string>
    <string name="menu_close">Drawer Close</string>

    <string name="text_eeg">At the <b>Emirates Environmental Group </b>, we believe in the power of action to create a <b>sustainable future </b>. Make a difference by contributing to <i><b>Donate to Plant a Tree</b></i> where your generosity
        can help us reach our goal of planting thousands of <b>trees</b>. Your contributions help in fostering a greener planet.
        every donation counts, with contributions up to <b>50,000 dirhams</b>.</string>

    <string name="aboutUsInfo"> Welcome to <i><b>ClimateHope Fund </b></i> a pioneering project dedicated to fighting <b> climate change and promoting sustainability.</b>
    With strong connections to renowned organizations, our app facilitates both donations and volunteering opportunities. Your contributions, whether through donations or volunteering, directly fuel our collective mission.
    Partnering with esteemed organizations amplifies the impact of every action you take. Join us today in the fight for a more sustainable tomorrow, where ClimateHope Fund serves as your ally in building a
    resilient and thriving planet. Together, let\'s pave the way for a
    future where the echoes of our efforts resonate for generations to come. Join us in advocating for a greener, more resilient future together.
</string>

    <string name="educ1"> <b>Climate change</b> refers to long-term alterations in the Earth\s climate patterns, primarily driven by human activities such as the <b> burning of fossil fuels</b> and  <b>deforestation </b>. The increase in greenhouse gas emissions, particularly carbon dioxide,
        traps heat in the atmosphere, leading to a rise in global temperatures. This warming contributes to various environmental impacts, including more frequent and severe weather events, rising sea levels,
             and disruptions to ecosystems.
        Climate change poses significant threats to biodiversity, human health, and socio-economic stability, <b> Donating to climate change </b>efforts helps fund crucial initiatives aimed at mitigating environmental threats fostering <b>sustainable</b> practices and safeguarding the planet.</string>

    <string name="effects_climate_ch">Climate change manifests in a range of severe effects, including rising global temperatures, leading to more frequent and intense heatwaves. Melting ice caps and glaciers contribute to rising sea levels, threatening coastal communities and low-lying areas. Extreme weather events, such as hurricanes, floods, and droughts, become more frequent and unpredictable, impacting agriculture, water resources, and infrastructure. Ocean acidification, a result of increased carbon dioxide absorption, poses a threat to marine ecosystems and fisheries. Shifts in ecosystems and biodiversity loss occur as species struggle to adapt to changing conditions. These interconnected effects highlight the urgent need for
        global efforts to mitigate climate change and promote sustainable practices.</string>

    <style name="SemiBoldInter">
        <item name="android:fontFamily">@fonts/Inter-SemiBold.ttf</item>
    </style>

    <string name="title_activity_main2">MainActivity2</string>
    <string name="title_home">Home</string>
    <string name="title_dashboard">Dashboard</string>
    <string name="title_notifications">Notifications</string>

    <!--    <style name="MySearchViewStyle" parent="Widget.AppCompat.SearchView">-->
    <!--        <item name="android:background">@color/dark_grey</item>-->

    <!--        &lt;!&ndash; Customize the hint text color &ndash;&gt;-->
    <!--        <item name="android:queryHint">@color/black</item>-->

    <!--        &lt;!&ndash; Customize the search icon color &ndash;&gt;-->
    <!--        <item name="searchIcon">@color/white</item>-->

    <!--    </style>-->

</resources>